▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 女单1/4决赛
高芙 6-2 6-2 科斯秋克 · 赛后场上采访
It's about when there's
一般都是网前握手不太友好时
an unfriendly handshake at the net.
大家才会拿出来说
I think we needed to talk
但这次这么友好
about how friendly that was.
我觉得也值得聊聊
It was a lot of smiles,
两个人一直在笑
a lot of respect for each other.
也都非常尊重对方
Shows how classy you are as a player.
看得出你是个很有风度的球员
No, yeah, Marta is a a great opponent
是的 玛尔塔是个很棒的对手
or opponent.
不 对手……
I meant to say person.
我想说的是人
Also a a tough opponent, too.
也是个很难打的对手
But no, she's someone I have a lot
总之 她是我非常
of respect for.
尊重的人
Even before the match,
比赛开始前
we were chatting about US Open.
我们还在聊美网
So, she's definitely one
所以我觉得她绝对是巡回赛里
of I think the most talented
最有天赋的球员之一
and athletic players on tour and yeah,
身体能力也非常出色
tonight I just played really well
今晚是我自己打得很好
and you know,
而且你也知道
a lot of respect cuz I know it wasn't
我很尊重她 因为我知道今晚
her best night,
她没有打出最好水平
but obviously great sportsmanship
但她展现了很好的体育精神
from her.
这点很难得
It was a great night for you.
今晚对你来说很精彩
You're through to another Masters 1000.
你又一次闯进1000赛
You do so well in the 1000s.
你在1000赛总是打得很好
What is it about these kind of tournaments
这类赛事有什么特别之处
that bring out the best in you?
能让你打出最好的自己？
Definitely playing in front
当然少不了
of this home crowd.
主场观众的支持
Yeah.
是这样
Shout out to
特别要谢谢……
I don't know who was saying I'm in love
不知道刚才是谁在喊
with the Coco, but I like that one.
「我爱Coco」 但我很喜欢
You guys are the best. That was a good one.
你们太会了 这句喊得好
And it's the right Coco.
而且喊的是对的那个Coco
So Sorry.
所以……抱歉
I was Never mind.
我刚才……算了
Next question.
下一个问题吧
Okay, next question.
好 下一个问题
You're making me blush.
你们都把我说脸红了
But let's just talk a little bit
还是来聊聊
about your level of play.
你现在的竞技状态吧
You're in such a good place.
你现在处在很好的位置
You're moving around the court great.
场上移动也很出色
You're serving well. What are you happiest
发球同样很好 打进半决赛
with about moving into the semifinals
准备迎战萨拉时
against Sara?
你最满意的是哪一点？
Yeah,
是这样
I think just staying aggressive today.
今天我一直主动进攻
Marta's someone who can take control
玛尔塔很容易就能掌控
of the point very easily and I was just trying
一分球的主动 所以我努力
to do my best to defend the balls I needed
在该防守的球上尽力顶住
to and then be aggressive
有机会时再主动进攻
when I could and obviously the next match
至于下一场
is going to be tough against Sara.
对萨拉肯定会很难打
She's had some incredible wins,
她赢下了几场精彩的比赛
but I'm looking forward to the challenge.
但我很期待这个挑战
Yeah, we can't wait to see what's in store.
我们也等不及看接下来会怎样
Ladies and gentlemen, Coco Gauff.
女士们先生们 高芙
Let's hear it for her. Through
把掌声送给她 她已经
to the semifinals.
打进半决赛